One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The Sake I Brewed to Drink With You
Seninle İçmek İçin Hazırladığım Sake
The island is flying?!
Ada uçuyor mu?
Can this... truly be happening?!
Böyle bir şey mümkün mü?
Just how powerful is Kaido?!
Nasıl bir adam bu Kaido?
What?!
Ne?!
Why?!
Niye?!
How come?!
Nasıl?!
Marco the Phoenix?!
Anka Kuşu Marco mu?!
Marco the Phoenix Former Whitebeard Pirate
"Anka Kuşu" Marco Eski Beyazsakal Korsanları Üyesi
Well then, let's try this!
Öyleyse... bu iş görür!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
Ay! Ay, ay, ay!
Chopper!
Chopper-san!
Hot! Hot! I'm burning!
Yanıyorum, aman! Diri diri yanıyorum!
Hey! That's going too far!
Hey! Isıtacağına yaktın hayvanı...
I thought we were on the same side!
Aynı taraftayız zannetmiştim...
Marco!
Marco-san!
Marco...!
Marco...!
They sure are testy...
Hemen parlıyor bunlar da.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay...
Chopper! I'll put it out!
Chopper-san, hemen söndürüyorum seni.
It's burning my arm!
Kolum alev aldı!
It'll scorch me too–
Ben de cayır cayır–
Or not?
Yanlış alarm.
This flame...
Bu alev...
Ouch! Ouch! Ow, ow...
Ah! Ay! Ay, ay...
Chopper, you can relax!
Chopper, sakinleş.
Huh?
Ha?
It's really hot–
Ay ay!
Or not?
Yanlış alarm.
I'm on fire but I'm not getting burned!
Alev aldığım hâlde yanmıyorum.
This flame is comfortably...
Bu alevin rahatlatan bir...
warm...
sıcaklığı var.
– Dr. Chopper!
– Dr. Chopper!
We're ready to produce the antibodies!
Antikor üretimi için her şey hazır!
Come quickly!
Bir an önce buraya gelin!
Miyagi, Mink Doctor
Mink Doktoru, Miyagi Mink Hemşiresi, Tristan
It's a swarm of ice ogres!
Buz şeytanı sürüsü!
Miyagi! Tristan! Get out of here!
Miyagi, Tristan kaçın!
Gotta warm them up one way or another!
Madem herkes ısıtılmalı...
Phoenix Pyreapple!
Anka Pasif Alevi!
Yeow!
Yandım!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay...
Oh, it's not that hot...
Oh, o kadar da sıcak değil.
The chill in my body is fading!
Donmam kesildi.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Ay, ay, ay, ay...
What?!
Ne?!
Wh-What was I...?!
B-Ben ne...?!
Omasa!
Omasa!
Thank goodness! You came to your senses!
Şükürler olsun, bilincini tekrar kazandın.
Omasa...!
Omasa...!
Well, it's like you were saying. It's sapping your body heat.
Senin de dediğin gibi, vücut sıcaklıkları artıyor.
Once your stamina runs out, you'll turn back into an ogre!
Dayanacak güçleri kalmayınca tekrar şeytana dönecekler.
I only bought you a bit of time!
Size biraz vakit kazandırdım, o kadar.
You're a lifesaver!
Sağ ol!
Time's just what the doctor ordered!
Tek istediğim buydu.
Miyagi! Tristan!
Miyagi! Tristan!
Are you two okay?!
İyi misiniz?
Y-Yes!
E-Evet!
We're fine!
İyiyiz!
Let's hurry and get to work!
İşe koyulalım!
We'll give you the support you need!
Biz de sana yardım edeceğiz!
Thank you! I can focus if I'm in that tower!
Sağ olun! O kulede üretime yoğunlaşabilirim.
Marco!
Marco!
He and that damn tanuki really know how to chap my ass!
O dallama da tanuki bozuntusu da eğlencemin içine ettiler!
Hey, you bums! Catch that tanuki already!
Yakalasanıza lan şu tanukiyi!
Why would he bother saving your lousy asses?!
Sizi kurtaracağını cidden düşündünüz mü?!
But... that tanuki...
Ama o tanuki...
Keep your eyes on the prize!
Tereddüte düşmeyin!
If you don't wanna bite the dust, crush that tanuki and take back the antibody!
Canınızı seviyorsanız o tanukiyi temizleyip antikoru geri alın!
I see... I think I've got the gist of the situation.
Burada neler döndüğünü aşağı yukarı anladım.
Hey, Roronoa!
Hey, Roronoa!
Weren't you on your way to slice 'n dice Kaido?
Gidip Kaido'yu kesmeyecek misin?
If you wanna get to the rooftop...
Çatı katına gitmek istiyorsan...
I'll give you a lift!
seni oraya uçurabilirim.
You guys are too good to be dealing with these chumps!
Siz de ayak takımıyla uğraşmak istemezsiniz herhâlde.
But Chopper needs our support...!
Fakat biz Chopper-san'a yardım etmeliyiz.
Don't worry... Sir Skeleton!
Merak etmeyin, İskelet-san!
We'll hold the line for Sir Tanuki!
Tanuki-san'ı biz kollarız!
Thanks, you guys! I'm counting on you!
Güveniyorum size.
Hold it, you son of a bitch!
Gel lan buraya it.
Apoo!
Apoo!
Give me back the antibody...!
Antikoru geri ver!
If I lose it...
Onu kaybedersem...
my ass is freakin' grass!
hayatım biter!
Give it a rest!
Bir rahat ver!
He won't stay down!
Dişli bir rakip.
I don't mind taking on one more job!
Hadi şu işi de aradan çıkaralım!
Sir Tanuki, hurry into the tower!
Tanuki-san, siz kuleye geçin.
– Apoo!
– Apoo-san!
X Drake Formerly of the Soaring Six Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit: Allosaurus
X Drake Tobi Roppo'nun Eski Üyesi Ejderha-Ejderha Meyvesi Antik Model: Allosaurus
This guy...
Bu herif...
Drake?!
Drake-san?!
So he really has switched sides!
Harbi taraf değiştirmiş!
Roronoa Zoro. If you would consider me an ally...
Roronoa Zoro, beni sizden biri olarak görüyorsan...
then I'll hold them here while you go ahead!
burayı bana bırakıp önden git!
At least you know how to bet on the winning horse!
Doğru ata oynamayı biliyorsun.
4th Floor Inside the Castle
4. Kat Kalenin İçi
Sanji! Sanji!
Sanji! Sanji!
Perhaps Sanji sensed a powerful foe and went to hold them back on the third floor!
Sanji üçüncü katta güçlü bir düşman sezip onu durduruyor olmalı.
Maybe...!
Olabilir...!
Guess my observation haki isn't that good yet.
Gözlem hakimi geliştirmem lazım.
I'm not picking up Sanji's presence at all!
Sanji'nin yerini, hatta varlığını bile sezemiyorum.
Do you feel something, Jinbe?!
Bir şeyler seziyor musun, Jinbe?
Yeah...
Evet.
There are quite a few enemies in here...
Sayıları çok fazla.
And...
Üstelik...
they're quite strong!
güçlüler de.
Seems like one of us should remain on this floor!
İçimizden biri bu katta kalsa iyi olacak.
I'll create an opening. You go on ahead!
Dikkatlerini üzerime çekeceğim, sen devam et.
Let's do this!
Kollayın kendinizi!
General...
General...
Launcher!
Roketatarı!
Right-Brain Tower Inside the Dome
Sağ Beyin Kulesi Kubbenin İçi
Time to raise a little hell!
Şimdi geliyor gelmekte olan!
General...
General...
Cannon!
Topu!
Get back, men!
Geri çekilin!
Who the hell fires something so haphazardly?!
Moron gibi her tarafa ateş ediyorsun.
You're asking for it!
Kendini bir halt sanma ulan!
I dig the look, bro!
Vay babam vay.
A triceratops!
Triceratops!
Sasaki Soaring Six Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit: Triceratops
Sasaki Tobi Roppo Ejderha-Ejderha Meyvesi Antik Model: Triceratops
So you're a dinosaur!
Dinozormuşsun sen de.
Just give up! This is the strongest creature that ever lived!
Teslim ol. Tarihin en güçlü canlısı bu!
You'll be nothing but scrap when I'm done with you!
Seni paramparça edip hurdaya çevireceğim!
There's no scratching the sheen of Wapometal!
Wapo metalinin ışıltısını yok et de göreyim!
Outside the Onigashima Dome
Onigashima Kubbesinin Dışında
It's the Soaring Six!
Tobi Roppo!
Ulti Soaring Six Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit: Pachycephalosaurus
Ulti Tobi Roppo Ejderha-Ejderha Meyvesi Antik Model: Pachycephalosaurus Page One Tobi Roppo Ejderha-Ejderha Meyvesi Antik Model: Spinosaurus
Where did they go?!
Nereye gitti bunlar?
I am ever so vexed!
Kafayı yiyeceğim sinirden.
I shall crack her detestable head wide open! That bitch!
O şıllığın kafasından kıvılcım çıkaracağım!
He ran off that way!
O yöne kaçtı.
Banquet Hall 3rd Floor Inside the Castle
Ziyafet Salonu 3. Kat Kalenin İçi
Banquet Hall 3rd Floor Inside the Castle
Ziyafet Salonu 3. Kat Kalenin İçi
Banquet Hall 3rd Floor Inside the Castle
Ziyafet Salonu 3. Kat Kalenin İçi
Banquet Hall 3rd Floor Inside the Castle
Ziyafet Salonu 3. Kat Kalenin İçi
Slow down, silly!
Dur bakayım!
Wait for us!
Beklesene!
Damn! What is this?!
Hay! Bu ne be?
Let me out!
Çözün beni hemen!
You can stop struggling now...
Debelenirmiş de.
Be a good boy... Don't try to run.
Ayıp, kaçıyorsun.
After all...
Demedin mi...
didn't you say that you loved me?
beni sevdiğini?
Black Maria Soaring Six Ancient Spider-Spider Fruit: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Tobi Roppo Örümcek-Örümcek Meyvesi Antik Model: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Soaring Six Ancient Spider-Spider Fruit: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Tobi Roppo Örümcek-Örümcek Meyvesi Antik Model: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Soaring Six Ancient Spider-Spider Fruit: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Tobi Roppo Örümcek-Örümcek Meyvesi Antik Model: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Soaring Six Ancient Spider-Spider Fruit: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Tobi Roppo Örümcek-Örümcek Meyvesi Antik Model: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Soaring Six Ancient Spider-Spider Fruit: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Tobi Roppo Örümcek-Örümcek Meyvesi Antik Model: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Soaring Six Ancient Spider-Spider Fruit: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Black Maria Tobi Roppo Örümcek-Örümcek Meyvesi Antik Model: Rosamygale Grauvogeli
Stay by my side forever. I'll make you my pet.
Ebediyen burada kalsana. Oyuncağım ol.
Don't be ridiculous! I...
Saçmalama! Gitmem...
I have somewhere to be!
Gitmem gerekiyor!
But...
Ama...
everywhere...
hangi yöne...
I look...
bakarsam bakayım...
it's women, women, women...!
hep kadın var.
Is this...
Burası...
heaven?
cennet mi?
He's clearly lost it.
Aklını kaçırmış.
You're absolutely precious...
Çok tatlış bir şeysin sen.
Big Cat Cafe 4th Floor
Büyük Kedi Kafeteryası 4. Kat
So Straw Hat went on ahead...
Hasır Şapka önden gitti.
This'll be a real headache for ol' Kaido...
Kaido-san'ın canını sıkacaktır.
Would you kindly stop...
Adamlarımla uğraşmayı...
picking on my men?
keser misin?
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's-Who Tobi Roppo Kedi-Kedi Meyvesi Antik Model: Kılıç Dişli Kaplan
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's-Who Tobi Roppo Kedi-Kedi Meyvesi Antik Model: Kılıç Dişli Kaplan
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's-Who Tobi Roppo Kedi-Kedi Meyvesi Antik Model: Kılıç Dişli Kaplan
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's-Who Tobi Roppo Kedi-Kedi Meyvesi Antik Model: Kılıç Dişli Kaplan
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's-Who Tobi Roppo Kedi-Kedi Meyvesi Antik Model: Kılıç Dişli Kaplan
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's-Who Tobi Roppo Kedi-Kedi Meyvesi Antik Model: Kılıç Dişli Kaplan
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's-Who Tobi Roppo Kedi-Kedi Meyvesi Antik Model: Kılıç Dişli Kaplan
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's-Who Tobi Roppo Kedi-Kedi Meyvesi Antik Model: Kılıç Dişli Kaplan
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's-Who Tobi Roppo Kedi-Kedi Meyvesi Antik Model: Kılıç Dişli Kaplan
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's-Who Tobi Roppo Kedi-Kedi Meyvesi Antik Model: Kılıç Dişli Kaplan
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's-Who Tobi Roppo Kedi-Kedi Meyvesi Antik Model: Kılıç Dişli Kaplan
Who's-Who Soaring Six Ancient Cat-Cat Fruit: Saber-Toothed Tiger
Who's-Who Tobi Roppo Kedi-Kedi Meyvesi Antik Model: Kılıç Dişli Kaplan
Former Warlord Jinbe, Knight of the Sea, acting with all the decorum of a child?
Eski Shichibukai, Denizin Şövalyesi Jinbe çocuk gibi davranıyor.
I am the helmsman of the Straw Hats!
Hasır Şapkalar'ın dümencisiyim ben.
Would you do me the honor of using this worthier title?
Bu unvanımı kullanmanı yeğlerim.
Oh, my bad.
Ah, affola.
I caught a glimpse of you back in your Warlord days...
Shichibukai olduğun dönem görmüştüm seni.
What?!
Ne?!
Well, it's no big deal.
Unut gitsin dediğimi.
Who are you?
Sen kimsin?
Man, who could I possibly be?
Kimim, sen söyle.
Perhaps removing your mask will jog my memory.
Maskeni çıkarayım, kimmişsin anlarım.
I'd love to see you try.
Olmayacak duaya amin deme.
Forbidden Storehouse Inside the Dome
Kubbenin İçindeki Yasaklı Depo
We can hide here for a bit since this room has long gone unnoticed.
Pek kimse bakmadığından bir süre burada saklanabiliriz.
What am I seeing?
Bu nedir?
A statue of a dragon.
Ejderha heykeli.
It once stood at the entry point of the island, but it was placed in here after my friend broke it.
Eskiden adanın girişindeydi ama arkadaşım kırınca buraya koyduk.
Your friend?
Arkadaşın mı?
Yes...
Evet...
A few years ago...
Birkaç yıl önce tanıştık.
he came to kill my father!
Babamı öldürmeye gelmişti.
What gives? This place is deserted...
Hayda, kimse yok mu?
Intruders!
İşgalciler!
If you're not Kaido, get lost!
Benim işim Kaido'yla!
Ace!
Ace!
Guys, go save the children while you can!
Siz fırsat varken çocukları kurtarın!
Got it!
Anlaşıldı!
Leave it to us!
Bize bırak!
This one won't stay down!
Keçi gibi inatçı!
Who are you?! Tell me your name!
Sen kimsin? Adını söyle!
Right back at you!
Önce sen!
I'm Ace!
Adım Ace!
I'm here to take Kaido's head!
Kaido'nun kellesini almaya geldim!
I found them! Over here!
Buldum onları! Buraya gelin!
Don't be scared. We're getting all of you out of here.
Korkmayın, sizi kurtarmaya geldik.
Yeah, but we need to hurry.
Hadi kalkın gidelim.
You're pretty tough.
Güçlüsün.
Ace!
Ace!
All the children are okay!
Çocuklar güvende.
But we can't find Kaido anywhere!
Ama hedefimiz Kaido ortalıkta yok!
What?!
Ne?!
My father went on an expedition!
Babamlar keşif gezisinde.
At this very moment...
Şu anda bu adada...
not a single officer is here!
tek bir rütbeli yok!
Your father?!
Baba derken?
– What?!
– Ne?!
So she's Kaido's daughter?!
Kaido'nun kızı mı bu?
I'm Yamato!
Benim adım Yamato!
I think it's about time you stopped tearing up the place!
Bu kadar ortalığı yakıp yıktığımız yeter.
If you have time to wonder who I am,
Kim olduğumu soracak vaktiniz varsa...
then you have time to leave and return these children to their families!
hemen burayı terk edip o çocukları ailelerine kavuşturun!
I'll take you up on that.
Teklifini kabul ediyorum.
But is it wise to let us go?
Gitmemize izin vermen sorun olmasın?
It's not like I'm under any obligation to protect this island.
Bu adayı korumak gibi bir görevim yok.
Alright, let's get back to Wano.
Hadi Wano'ya dönelim.
Your families are waiting for you.
Aileleriniz sizi bekliyor.
Truly, we can't thank you enough!
Ne kadar teşekkür etsek az.
You sure, Ace?
Son kararın mı Ace?
That means going back to the mainland without you.
Biz sensiz ana karaya dönüyoruz.
That's right. Keep them safe. I'll catch up later.
Evet, çocuklar size emanet. Sonra size katılırım.
I'm not convinced someone as strong as you isn't at least one of their captains...
Böyle güçlü birinin kaptan falan olmayışını aklım almıyor.
Let's settle this!
Hesabımızı kapatalım!
I was bored anyway.
Benim de canım sıkılıyordu zaten.
Let's fight!
Dövüşelim!
Fire Fist!
Ateş Yumruk!
What's the story? Shouldn't someone as strong as you be out at sea?!
Neden? Bu kadar güçlü olduğun hâlde neden denize açılmıyorsun?
It's all his fault...
Onun suçu.
Kaido's fault!
Kaido'nun!
Of all the people to have as a father...
Öyle biri babam.
It's all your father's fault?
Babanın suçu mu?
That's your excuse?
Bahane mi arıyorsun?
You can't...
Anne babamızı...
choose your parents, Yamato!
seçemeyiz, Yamato!
Shut up! Don't you think I know that?!
Kes sesini! Demesen de farkındayım!
Do you really?
Emin misin?
Physical shackles are one thing, but if you hate your father this much...
Babandan bu kadar nefret ediyorsan ellerini geçtim...
why shackle your heart as well?!
ne diye kalbine de zincir vurduruyorsun?
Yamato!
Yamato!
What do you want to do?!
Asıl isteğin nedir?
I admit...
Kendimi...
I was holding myself back.
baskıladığımı kabul ediyorum.
But now I realize...
Şimdi gözlerim açıldı.
I wanna set out to sea and go on adventures!
Ben de denize açılıp maceralara atılmak istiyorum!
I wanna live freely like Oden!
Oden gibi özgürce yaşamak istiyorum!
Set out to sea...
Denize...
I wanna leave this damn island...!
Bu lanet adadan kurtulup...
I wanna live freely!
özgürce yaşamak istiyorum!
That's the spirit, Yamato!
Ha şöyle, Yamato!
It's good to want those things!
Doğru yolu buldun.
Now you know what to do.
Bir karara vardın.
Yeah!
Evet!
And he came home in tatters!
Sonra da eve dayak yemiş hâlde geldi.
When we were kids, he got us into all kinds of trouble!
Çocukken az yaramaz değildi.
Your little brother sure is something!
Kardeşin alemmiş.
Right?!
Öyledir.
So tell me, what's it like out there?!
Dışarıda işler ne durumda?
Are there a lot of young up-and-comers?!
Gençler nam peşinde koşuyor mu?
Young...? Let me think...
Gençler mi? Bir düşüneyim.
Everyone's talking about Caven-something.
Caven bilmem ne diye biri çok konuşuluyor.
Yeah?!
Öyle mi?!
Well, I'm in a class of my own,
Rakipsiz beni saymazsak...
but I heard some dangerous guys are running wild in every sea.
her denizde belalı tiplerin çıkış yaptığı duyumları aldım.
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
Hıhı! Hıhı!
There's Kid in the south...
Güney denizinde Kid,
Law in the north and Bege in the west.
kuzeyde Law ve batıda Bege.
But the toughest one of all will set sail in a few years...
Ama en adından söz edilecek adam birkaç yıla gelecek.
My kid brother!
Kardeşim olur kendisi!
He'll blow 'em all outta the water!
Büyük biri olacağına inancım tam!
You sure do like to talk about your brother.
Kardeşin de kardeşin, daha ne kadar bahsedeceksin?
So what?! You should listen!
1 milyon kere de olsa dinle!
Ow, ow, ow!
Ay, ay, ay!
You... That hurts!
Seni ayyaş!
H-Hey, stop!
Hey, y-yapma!
The truth is I'm the one who broke this dragon statue first.
Aslında bu heykeli ilk kıran bendim.
But he said...
Ama dedi ki...
"Let this be a warning to Kaido that I'll be back!"
"Kaido için geri geleceğim, ayağını denk alsın."
I see...
Anlıyorum...
I was unaware that a pirate once tried to save Wano...
Wano'yu kurtarmaya çalışan bir korsan olduğunu bilmiyordum.
It pissed off my father,
Babam köpürdü tabii.
but in the end, he never met Ace.
Hiç Ace'le karşılaşma fırsatı bulamadı.
Wait...
Bir dakika.
Your father?
Baban mı?
Didn't I mention Kaido being my father?
Babam Kaido demedim mi?
Wha– Hey, don't be so scared!
Ne– Hey, korkmayın o kadar!
Hey, but I really do hate him!
Ben de ondan nefret ediyorum.
Like I said, I'm Oden!
Oden'im demiştim, değil mi?
That is even more confusing!
Daha da aklımız karıştı!
I'm not scary! I hate Kaido!
Benden korkmayın, ben de Kaido'dan nefret ediyorum.
I longed for the sea and adventure, so I became Oden, who lived freely!
Deniz ve macera hayaliyle özgürce yaşayan Oden oldum.
We understand for the most part.
Konuyu anladık.
Thank you for tending to us!
İlk yardım için minnettarız.
Stop being so formal and get over here!
Resmiyeti kesip yanıma gelin!
But Yamato,
Peki Yamato...
where is this would-be savior of Wano now?
Wano'yu kurtarmaya çalışmış o adam şu an nerede?
Ace...
Ace...
died two years ago.
iki yıl önce öldü.
Otama, you knew Ace?!
Otama, Ace'i tanıyor musun?
Yes, he was like a brother to me!
Evet, çok yakındık.
I decided to believe in Ace and try to become a kunoichi,
Ace'e inanarak kunoichi olmak istedim...
but Big Bro Luffy was mean and said to me...
ama Luffy ağabey pat diye...
Ace is dead.
Ace öldü.
He said it to me out of the blue.
...onun öldüğünü söyledi.
It made me so sad.
Çok üzüldüm.
Oh, sorry about that.
Evet, kusura bakma.
That's just the way he is.
O da böyle biri.
But y'know, Otama, it was really hard for Luffy, too.
Ama Otama, Luffy de çok acı çekti.
Back when it happened...
O olayda...
Huh?
Ha?
He's ruining it!
Hadsiz!
Listen up, folks!
Dinleyin!
Put a stop to Marco!
Marco'yu durdurun!
Don't let him run free!
Dilediğini yapmasın!
C'mon, he saved us...
Adam bizi kurtardı.
But if we don't do what His Awesomeness wants, he'll kill us anyway...
Öyle de Queen-sama bizi öldürsün mü?
Don't just stand there!
Tereddüt etmeyin!
I gave you an order!
Emrimi yerine getirin!
I won't be facing Kaido directly at this point.
Şu an Kaido'ya doğrudan saldırmak gibi bir niyetim yok.
Nico Robin! Skeleton Man! You've got places to be!
Nico Robin, İskelet Adam, siz görevinizi yapın!
Get to the castle!
Kaleye koşun!
Now's our chance.
Gidelim!
If you insist!
Siz öyle diyorsanız.
Go to hell, Marco!
Geber Marco!
You're finished, Marco the Phoenix!
İşin bitti, Anka Kuşu Marco!
You ready?
Hazır mısın?
Do it!
Evet!
Damn that Marco!
Marco piçi...
Nice going!
İyiymiş böyle.
You're pretty relaxed for someone about to face down an Emperor!
Yonko Kaido'ya doğru gidiyorsun ama çok rahatsın.
Why should I be scared of Kaido?
Kaido'dan korkmak ne işime yarayacak?
If my captain gives the order, I follow it.
Kaptanım bir emir verdiyse ona uyarım.
Look at me, rooting for Straw Hat– No...
Ben de Hasır Şapka'ya güveniyorum. Hayır...
rooting for all you Worst Generation punks!
En Kötü Nesil'e.
I wonder how he would've felt hearing his brother picked a fight with an Emperor, too...
Kardeşinin bir Yonko'yla kavgaya tutuşacağını bilseydi ne tepki verirdi acaba?
I'm begging you, Pops!
N'olur babalık.
I said no, you little shit!
Olmaz dedim, ahmak.
Ace, I've told you plenty of times now...
Kaç defa anlattım sana Ace.
who the 2nd Division commander was before you...
Senden önceki 2. tümen komutanının kim olduğunu...
and why the position was vacant for so long.
ve o koltuğun neden uzun bir süre boş kaldığını.
Wano practices a policy of isolation, so information never comes out.
Wano dış dünyaya kapalı olduğundan içeriden haber alamıyoruz.
We were unaware that Lord Oden had died until several years after the fact.
Biz dahi ölümünü birkaç yıl sonra öğrendik.
We toyed with the idea of raiding Wano, but to what end?
Wano'ya yürümeyi düşündük ama sonuçlarını hesaba katmalıyız.
Can you imagine the toll it would take?
Bedeli ne olur hiç kafa yordun mu?
The toll?
Bedeli mi?
Then, let me go by myself!
Tek benim gitmeme izin ver o zaman!
I made a promise...
Bir söz verdim.
Kozuki Oden couldn't take that guy down...
Kozuki Oden'in yenemediği adamı...
Meaning you couldn't beat him on your best day!
sen nasıl yeneceksin?
Don't overestimate yourself, Ace!
Kendini bu kadar büyük görme, Ace!
Y'know, Oden's strength was the real deal!
Oden çok güçlüydü anasını satayım.
You really wanna take down the big shots, Commander Ace!
Demek gerçekten de büyük isimleri devirmek niyetindesin, Komutan Ace!
Give it a rest, Teach!
Kes sesini, Teach.
Ace isn't motivated by hunting "big shots."
Ace büyük isimleri devirmek istemiyor.
Dammit...
Siktir.
I need to get stronger so I can fulfill my promise...
Güçlenmezsem sözümü tutamam.
That's what you're shouldering, huh?
Bütün meselen buymuş demek...
Ace, if Pops ever gives the go-ahead, do not forget to extend an invitation my way.
Babalıktan izni koparırsan Ace, beni de davet edersin.
Count me in, too.
Beni de say.
In that case, we can probably kick his ass now...
Artık onu yenebiliriz o zaman.
How are you still overestimating the situation...?
İyimser olunur da bu kadar mı olunur?
Marco!
Marco!
Don't think we'd just let you through!
Burayı kolayca geçebileceğini sanma!
Superstar Queen Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit: Brachiosaurus
Önder Queen Ejderha-Ejderha Meyvesi Antik Model: Brachiosaurus
Besides, all the samurai up top are dead by now!
Ayrıca dışarıdaki samuraylar da şimdiye kadar nalları dikmiştir.
And when Kozuki Oden's son is dead, the battle will be over!
Kozuki Oden'in oğlu da ölsün, bu savaş sona erecek.
Superstar King Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit: Pteranodon
Önder King Ejderha-Ejderha Meyvesi Antik Model: Pteranodon
Wano shall be reborn as the pirate empire of New Onigashima!
Wano da Yeni Onigashima ismiyle korsan imparatorluğuna dönüşecek!
If that's what you believe, then you really have a screw loose!
Sahiden buna inanıyorsanız beyniniz ölmüş!
Stop squawking, little bird!
Sus lan, kuş bozuntusu!
Damn! Is he invincible?!
Sikeyim! Yenilmez mi bu?
What kind of power is that?
Ne çeşit bir gücü var?
You're up against the force of a new era now!
Yeni çağla dövüşüyorsunuz!
The Beast Pirates will crush this "new era," along with everything else!
Canavar Korsanları her şeye olduğu gibi ona da hükmedecek!
Wha–
Ne–
Now, now... Just let him pass!
Hey, hey... Bırakın geçsin işte.
And up you go!
Hadi, dal içeri!
You seriously just threw me?!
Aniden niye fırlatıyorsun?
What?!
Ne?!
B...
L...
Big Bro Luffy is Ace's little bro?!
Luffy ağabey, Ace'in kardeşi mi?
That's right.
Evet.
You didn't know?
Bilmiyor muydun?
Because when I mentioned Ace, he said so casually...
Ben Ace'den bahsederken gayet sakince dedi ki...
Ace is dead.
Ace öldü.
I said some mean things to Big Bro...
Ağabeye çok kötü şeyler söyledim.
He would've been mean right back if it had bothered him.
Rahatsız olsaydı kızardı zaten.
Don't worry!
Takma kafana.
But...
Ama...
Big Bro... I'm sorry!
Ağabey, özür dilerim!
Like I said, don't worry.
Takma kafana diyorum.
Anyway, let's give this "Otama Strategy" of yours a shot!
O değil de demin dediğin planı uygulayalım.
Forbidden Storehouse Inside the Dome
Kubbenin İçindeki Yasaklı Depo
What?!
Ne?!
This person you speak of was Roger's son,
Roger'ın oğlu...
and Luffy's older brother?!
ve Luffy'nin ağabeyi mi o?
Is that true?!
Doğru mu bu?
Mm-hm.
Hıhı.
You all brought Luffy to Wano, right?
Luffy'yi Wano'ya siz getirmediniz mi?
That is correct...
Evet.
There are as many pirates as there are stars in the sky, but they're the ones you met...
Sayısız korsan arasında karşınıza çıkanlar onlardı,
and you brought them to this country...
ve siz de onları bu topraklara getirdiniz...
I can't imagine this as anything but fate!
Bunun kaderden başka bir açıklaması olamaz!
Because...
Çünkü...
Luffy's name bears the initial D!
Luffy'nin adında da "D." var!
Yummy!
Nefis!
Fire really hits the spot!
Ateş çok güzel.
Delicious!
Leziz!
I'm so stuffed now!
Tıka basa doydum!
I'm fully recharged!
Şarj oldum!
Did you finish your meals?
Yemek işiniz bitti mi?
Yes, Mama!
Evet, Mama!
I'm good to go!
Ben de hazırım.
Okay then, let's go!
Gidelim öyleyse.
Straw Hat isn't here yet?
Hasır Şapka daha gelmedi mi?
Hey, Kaido!
Hey, Kaido!
You can kill as many as you want as long as you leave Nico Robin alive.
Kimi öldürürsen öldür ama Nico Robin'e dokunma.
Don't you have a member of the three-eye people who can read the ancient script?
Şu sendeki üç gözlü, antik yazıları okuyamıyor mu?
Oh, Pudding?
Pudding mi?
I'm not sure she can.
Bilmem.
I can't wait for her true awakening anymore.
Uyanışını bekleyecek sabrım kalmadı.
Yeah, that make sense...
Mesele anlaşıldı.
5th Floor Inside the Castle
5.Kat Kalenin İçi
This is about all we can do to assist, so please, go on ahead!
Elimizden gelen bu kadar, geçin lütfen.
These are the stairs to the rooftop!
Çatı katına giden merdiven bu.
Thanks, Shishimamushi!
Sağ ol, Shishimamushi!
It's Shishilian.
Adım Shishilian.
Yeah, I'll never forget it...
Hayatınız pahasına...
The way you guys defended Raizo with your lives!
Raizo'yu koruduğunuzu asla unutmayacağım.
Thank you!
Sağ olun.
Later!
Görüşürüz.
So where are you planning on dropping this island?
Peki adayı nereye indireceksin?
There is a castle in the Flower Capital that symbolizes the Kozuki.
Çiçek Başkenti'nde Kozuki'yi temsil eden bir ada var.
I heard they're having a festival.
Şu an halk, dans edip eğleniyor.
Quite a lot of people will die.
Sayısız insan ölecek.
Who cares?
Hiç önemli değil.
It's easy to get more slaves...
Köleden bol ne var?
It'll be a glorious capital.
Görkemli bir başkent olacak.
And the lode poneglyph?
Peki yol poneglifi?
Is it there?
Orada değil mi?
Your true colors are already showing!
Hemen asıl niyetini belli etme!
Don't give me that!
Bana tepeden bakma!
You're like a little brother to me!
Hâlâ gözümde küçük kardeşten farksızsın.
On that day when Rocks was defeated at God Valley,
Tanrı Vadisi'nde Rocks Korsanları'nın dağıldığı gün...
I gave you the Mythical Fish-Fish Fruit.
sana mitolojik zoan olan Balık-Balık Meyvesi'ni vermiştim.
You're indebted to me for life, Kaido!
Bana hayatın boyunca borçlusun, Kaido.
Whatever!
Her neyse.
Let's go get it, then we'll talk!
Bunu o zaman konuşuruz.
Let's get the One Piece!
One Piece'i ele geçirince!